(Raj:)Really? Us gonna tell him?
SHELDON:
Who's going to tell whom about what?
Sheldon. Hey. Hi.
(Sheldon:)Your surprise confuses me. I live here.
(Howard:)Right.
(Howard:)So, listen, what are you doing
tomorrow afternoon?
(Sheldon:)-Be more specific.
-Four-thirty.
(Sheldon:)That's not afternoon. That's preevning.
(Penny:)-What?
-It's a time of day I invented.
(Sheldon:)It better defines the ambiguous period...
...between afternoon and evening:
preevning.
(Sheldon:)Fairly certain it will catch on
as it fills a desperate need.
(Raj:)Right, okay. What are you doing
tomorrow preevning?
(Sheldon:)Well, tomorrow's Saturday.
Saturday night is laundry night.
(Sheldon:)So I'll be spending the preevning
pre-sorting and pre-soaking.
Okay, what if I were to tell you...
...tomorrow at 4:30,
you could meet a woman...
...who has been scientifically chosen
to be your perfect mate?
(Sheldon:)I would snort in derision
and throw my arms in the air...